Carlos Humberto Tábora Flores

• Cell phone: (504) 9471-2840

• Email address: carltabo79@gmail.com

• Home address: Colonia Universidad, 9 y 10 avenida, 22-24 calle. Casa# 2405

Honduras, C.A.

Summary

Experienced in Quality control, stock markets, customer service, sales and marketing. Oriented towards results, with international vision. Capability of adapting to any working environment. Committed to a personal and professional development. Personnel management capabilities. Entrepreneurial spirit. Immediate availability.

Professional experience

Quality Control site in charge Central American Boiler

August 2014 – Present, San Pedro Sula, Honduras

- -In charge of foreseeing the quality assurance for all construction processes during mechanical erection of boiler.
- -Managing and assigning of construction drawings to supervisors for new job areas.
- -Elaboration of protocols for completion of jobs for finished processes or procedures.
- -Translating officer between the project supervision from boiler manufacturer.
- -Assurance of 100% welding quality of all structural and pressure parts, as well as non-destructive reports approval.
- -In charge of meeting international ASME code standards.
- -Coordination of material handling and logistics for project parts.

<u>Customer service Coordinator for Asia & Europe Markets.</u>

Day Trade The World

January 2011 – December 2013 San Jose, Costa Rica

- -Coordination of offline operations and trade support to our clients in Asia and Europe markets.
- -Provide our clients with the latest versions of our proprietary software.
- -Provide and monitor live support for the well handling and development of our platform to our clients around the world.
- -Provide our internal departments such as BA, BI, Compliance, with feedback on our software development and acceptance by clients.
- -Customer ticket solving
- -Technical support on Day trading technologies
- -Operations support for contacting ECN's and markets for resolution of trade conflicts.
- -Risk management experience
- -Trade desk contact for Morgan Stanley

Trading floor manager

Day trade the world

January 2009 – December 2010 (2 years) San Jose, Costa Rica.

- -In charge of managing the trading floor activities, recruitment of new students to the trading floor.
- -Provided orientation in trading strategies to students.
- -Presented periodic, reports of earnings-losses and projections to management.
- -Managed an average of 64 collaborators between two shifts involving NA markets and Asian markets.



Sales executive

Comunicaciones Globales

January 2006 – June 2007 San Pedro Sula, Honduras

- -Direct sales coordinator for the Northern and Caribbean region in audiovisual equipment.
- -Sales follow up as customer service approach.

Chief of purchasing and supplies

ICCE-Ingenieros Consultores y Constructores Electromecánicos

January 2005 – January 2006 San Pedro Sula, Honduras

- -In charge of placement and follow-up of orders, and invoice control, (Providers).
- -Inventory and assets control, provided maintenance for vehicle fleet.
- -Office maintenance and projects control.

Academic background

Currently studying "Business Management"

CEUTEC Universidad a distancia de UNITEC.

Extracurricular activities

Startup weekend participant November 2013.

Honduras Startup participant & runner-up November 2016.

Languages English (100%), Spanish (Native)

Software FINRA's Antimoney laundering diploma, MS Office: Advanced Excel, Passport (Morgan

Stanley trading platform), ProsperPro (Proprietary Platform), Chartware (Proprietary

Platform), MySQL (Basic queries), Secure CRT (Basic commands).

Personal references in Costa Rica

Herbert Rodriguez: General Manager at Rolosa S.A.

Telephone: (506) 8316-0000

Email: Herbert.rodriguez@hotmail.com

Rosalyn Alvarado: General Manager at Day Trade the world.

Telephone: (506) 8706-9009/2291-2651

Email: roalvara@omira.com

Ruben Guevara: Trader & Financial Analyst at BAC – Puesto de Bolsa.

Telephone: (506) 8990-2326 Email: gyruben@gmail.com

Hanzell Flores: General Ledger Telephone: (506) 7104-3574 Email: hanzellro@hotmail.com

Personal references in Honduras

Lic. Jairo García, R&M Logistics, Senior Accountant

Cellular: (504)9611-1609

Email: jflores1981@hotmail.com

MAE. Jesús Humberto Tábora: General Manager at Tábora y Flores Auditores y Consultores.

Cellular: (504) 9453-0083

Email: socio@taborayflores.com

MAE Evelyn Ruiz: General Manager at Id Marketing

Cellular: (504) 3375-7315

Email: ventasidmkt@gmail.com